Well, now that the shrine is over, we're off to the racetrack.
Let's go!
Is that your character?
I got the bread, so I'm going to the shrine.
This show is a variety show where Ana-chan tries all kinds of things.
Here's the first one, brake cleaner.
That's nice.
How's it going?
It's good.
Is it on?
Oh, there it is. There it is.
Oh, there it is, there it is.
It's so hot today. It's a beautiful day.
What's summer gonna be like?
If it's this hot in April, I wonder how hot it'll be in December.
No, it's cold in December.
I'm right.
You're right.
No, no, no.
The point is... that's what this is all about.
Yes, it is.
I'm not a comedian.
I'm not a comedian, so I don't know what I'm talking about.
Like, "This is just a joke." I don't know anything about comedy.
I don't know much about the world.
I don't know much about the world, so I tend to think, "Oh, that's right.
I told him it was hot in December too.
I'm too stupid.
I almost think it's hot in December too.
I figured it out, but it's a pattern I see a lot.
I wondered how she could take it so well, and then she'd get sick right away.
But you're so funny.
Mine? I don't make a lot of jokes.
That's why...
3F and Lawson.
Do you know what 3F means?
I don't know what that means.
Future.
Feeling.
FEELING
Family mart
Ami-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma
What?
I like it.
Nice, huh?
It's a good setup.
Oh, you mean, like, a boo-boo?
You're just being a jerk.
So you can say it with more confidence.
I said, "You're an amima.
You're an amima.
That's nice.
So, do you have any talent like that?
There are a lot of them.
Oh, no, there are.
You know, the artist who talks shit when he's drinking?
What's that?
An artist who talks shit at drinkers.
An artist who sass comedians when they drink?
Make fun of me.
But there's something out there.
Yes, there is.
Of course there are.
It's like, "I heard that...
Like, "Do something funny.
And female TV personalities who ask comedians for favors.
Please do something about it.
During the show.
Please do the opposite.
Like the ones who pretend they're doing it the other way.
And female announcers who cut off the comedian while he's still talking because they want to carry on too much.
That's enough.
That's a lot.
There were more than I expected.
No, it's because they keep asking.
You can't stop, can you?
I'm getting more and more nervous.
I'm just kidding.
That's what I've been doing lately.
You mean like that? The character.
I'm working on my Kamitsuki thingy.
A comedian.
Actually...
He doesn't care about comedians.
You should definitely use this place.
No, don't use it.
I'll use it!
Don't worry, you don't have to use it.
What about you, Hanae?
What's up?
What about the talent you don't like?
No, no, no.
I don't mind TV personalities.
Artists...
Basically.
Basically...
Well, I don't know.
I think you're trying too hard to be popular.
Artists are all...
I see.I see.
Like a drinking party.
Once, you know...
I was invited by a friend.
I thought I was going to have a drink with my friends.
I didn't expect the artist to go.
That's tough?
It was really hard.
There was this really famous artist.
He was singing all his songs.
I thought it was gross.
And everyone around me was like...
I don't mean to yell at them, but
I mean, it's not like I'm yelling or anything.
It's gross and scary.
I didn't want to be a part of it.
Gross and scary?
I haven't said that since.
Who's that?
I can't say.
Are you a veteran?
Like now?
No, no, no, no.
I'm a veteran.
I'm a lot more...
I'm bummed out.
You're the Mystics.
What?
No, it's not.
No?
I'm a senior toy.
Toys.
But not Mystyle.
It's an acronym, Sidear.
They'll never know.
You're a mystic!
I'm telling the truth!
Then you're Mistyll!
No, I'm not!
You're Mistyll!
No, it's not!
What?
No, it's not Miss Stills!
Give me a letter!
Like alphamet?
Initials?
No, no, no. An English band.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
You're Mystil.
No, not Mystil.
It's not Mystil, really.
You've already got, like, a hundred songs out there?
You've released a hundred, haven't you?
Then you're Mistyll.
No, it's not.
No? No?
No.
It's got katakana.
Eeeee!
It's in there.
Then it's Mistyll.
No, it's not.
Miss is child rain, right?
It's in there. It is, isn't it?
No, yeah, it's in there.
Okay, stop. I'm getting the hang of this.
I'm starting to get it.
It's a little bit...
You know, that kind of thing.
You're a mystic.
No, I didn't.
It's just for today. I'm sleepy.
Why don't you go to bed?
Shall we? Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm good. I've got 40 minutes.
Oh, you won't miss me?
It's okay. Do you want to drive for the kids?
Ten minutes.
Okay.
Okay, when you wake up, tell me what you want to eat most right now.
I don't think so.
When I wake up.
When I wake up?
When you wake up then, poof! That's the first thing you say when you wake up.
Please.
Happy.
Yeah, I'm happy.
Hey, what's up?
Are you okay?
My dream and the shrine from earlier, they got mixed up.
What did you dream about?
Thank you for watching.
Mr. Manam, I'd be happy to sing for you.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching!
I'm getting hungry.
Are you awake?
I'm up.
What do you want to eat?
I don't know.
Skoda.
What?
I want to eat at Skuda.
You want to eat at Skudas?
I just woke up from sleep. I want some now.
For Skoda?
I want it now, right before.
No, I just like the ones that look like it.
You were talking in your sleep.
What?
Hmm.
I didn't say that.
He said, "Believe in yourself and go.
I don't talk in my sleep.
Like Minimoni rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
I'm not saying that.
I didn't say that.
Well... here we are.
Thank you.
Ede?
We've arrived at Ooike Station
We're at Ooike Station.
You slept?
People are driving.
Well, good, I had a good sleep.
You had a good sleep?
Is this the first time you've been in a horse stall?
No, it's my first time.
I didn't expect it to be so big.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Here's the track.
This is where they run. There's seats.
They're going to watch it from there.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's beautiful. I've seen dirtier places.
I can imagine.
It's surprisingly clean.
And it's a local race.
I'm glad they let you in.
I'm glad.
I can't go to all the tracks.
Really?
Not at the Central.
I don't even get any work.
Thank you, Mr. Hoyuki.
Can't I get a job if I talk about horse races like this?
I'll have to go to work.
I feel sorry for him.
He's so foul-mouthed, I can't take it anymore.
Let's see what you think, shall we? The race.
Yes, I do.
Let's do it.
Let's do it all.
It's a beautiful day.
Allo Channel
Let's see if you can predict the race.
Yes, sir.
I can do about four races today.
How many do you want me to win?
Well...
It depends on how you buy.
If you win half of them, that's great.
I don't care if I lose a race or two.
I won't give up if I lose.
I won't give up even if I lose.
Look at this newspaper.
The paper?
Just look at the paper.
You ever read a newspaper?
No, not at all.
I didn't know they had newspapers now.
First newspaper, a racing paper?
Yeah.
First page spread.
It's tiny.
What are you talking about?
Look how tiny it is.
Nobody comes here to look at that.
The first big race, 2:30 p.m.
This is the first race.
This is one of the horses.
You mean this is the horse's name?
Yes. His name is Sabuno Takatora.
The main one.
Wide Sniper.
Joanne Vert.
Something like that.
There are 12 horses
Among the 12 horses
The horse that will win
The horse that will finish first or in the top 3
Predicting the
Oh!Ooh.
So we just have to decide who comes in first.
I guess so.
Let's start with that.
Maybe a pro.
He's got a preference.
I really do.
I'm most confident about the 20 rounds.
This guy's amazing.
He's not amazing.
That's amazing.
That's the one I did in the Derby.
Circles and triangles.
20 circles, then a circle.
That's a great circle.
A circle followed by a black triangle.
A circle followed by a black triangle?
Black triangle?
A triangle without color.
That's it. That's it.
Ultima Knight.
What?
You just said the answer.
It's just...
The trick.
Ultima Knight.
He's the second favorite.
What?
With all these symbols...
With all those symbols.
He should be the favorite.
But the next one is number 4, World Nakayama.
Why?
What's this?
Who wrote this?
I don't know who wrote this information.
Why do people believe it?
I don't get it.
I'm not fooled.
You don't even know who wrote it.
You scared me.
I almost believed it.
You know, this newspaper...
There's no such thing as number one.
This number one favorite...
It's decided by the ticket buyers.
It's decided by the customers.
Like a popularity contest.
But...
If there's this much on it...
People haven't found out about it yet.
It's a very good Ultima Knight.
No one knows about this.
What? That's amazing.
You're the only one who knows.
That's why I'm here.
Do you see the word "otz"?
I see it.
It's got numbers on it.
Double that number and you'll get your money back.
What do you mean?
If you put 10,000 yen on first place at Ultima Night, and you come in first place.
Now it's multiplied by 4.0, so 10,000 yen will come back as 40,000 yen.
I see.
30,000 yen worth.
Then somehow snipers are the best.
Wide sniper is 134.3x, so if you put 10,000 on it, you get 1,340,000.
What? Then...
That's definitely the way to do it!
Let's not do that again.
What's that horse video down there? When?
Now.
What's the big deal? The horse.
It's like, uh, Earl Nakayama.
Oh, he's so slim.
I look at his muscles, his body shape, and if he's sweating, I think he might be a little...
That's what we look at here.
Beautiful, this one.
Nakayama from Our Lady of the Valley?
Yes.
But the most popular horses are the most popular.
So what do we do?
Well, I don't know... I like high odds.
Then, a trifecta...
A trifecta?
I'm only going to guess one horse, and I'm going to guess the first one.
If I guessed all three, the odds would be even higher.
Oh!
For example, if you don't get the first 9 Ultimate...
First place 9?
Second place, then what do you think is the next strongest?
Let's see, Earl's Nakayama.
Earl Nakayama?
A woman.
If we spread all three in a row, we get nine in the first, four in the second, and that's a multiple of this row.
Look at that, 80 times, 400 times, 200 times, 90 times.
You're getting more, right?
Yeah.
Multiply that by 10,000 and you get 4 million, 800,000, 900,000.
Okay, that's it.So that's it then.
A tavern?
I'd be explaining to you how I sell fried chicken.
Well...
No, no, there's another way to look at it, but is that better?
Is that better?
Demilitarized?
I don't know.
Demilitant.
That's not much of a guess.
You can't hit these?
It means I have to hit them all.
So one is better?
One for now.
The first race, then.
I'll take one on the ground for now.
So you'll do the Ultimate Knight after all?
Yeah.
How much do you want to spend?
Ano, today.
100,000.
You're doing it?
There's a Japanese race.
How many are you going to do?
This is important.
Let's see...
Ten.
Oh, shit.
A little bit at a time.
Like 20,000.
Let's make it 20,000.
I'll make it 20,000.
I'll go with World Nakayama.
I'll put 20,000 on the winner.
I'll put 20,000 yen.
Mr. Hoshino, what criteria do you always use to choose a winner?
I...
When I'm doing it for real, I predict how it'll turn out.
"This is how it's going to go.
I'll go like this.
So...
Then it's going to go like this.
I'm just going to predict it.
It doesn't take much time.
Are you the kind of person who decides quickly?
I think that's totally fine.
It's changed.
The Ultimate Knight is now the favorite.
Is that me?
It's starting to show.
I quadrupled it.
I quadrupled it, and now it's tripled.
How long do you think it'll take?
Fix?
Industry.
2:30 p.m.
Tickets close in 11 minutes.
And you're going to keep changing things by then?
I'm tired.
Are you serious?
This is how I won the race.
Until it starts.
Does it feel like a really long time?
It does.
No, it doesn't.
It's not like the usual five or 10 minutes.
No, it's not.
It's really something.
I don't know what it is, but it's possible.
It was the most popular one this time.
But you had a hunch.
I chose Pan.
Sometimes a horse comes along that I really don't know about.
Someone who's not a strong candidate.
That's true.
It seems like it's limited to you.
I don't know which horse it is, so...
I'll just remember the numbers.
Nine.
How many times around?
One lap.
Look.
Start.
It's starting.
It begins
It has begun
It has begun.
Where?
Number nine.
Where is it?
That's number four!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It changes between rounds.
Even number five. It's over.
Look, look.
Leader number three.
I'm on 9.
You're on three.
Number three.
Do you fall down sometimes?Do you fall down sometimes?
Yeah, I do.
I'm definitely tired.
That's funny.
He's funny.
Where is he?
He's here.
At the top.
Ultima Knight!
He's in the lead.
Where is it?
He's in the lead!
They didn't get past us.
They didn't get past me.
I'm in! I'm in!
He just moved.
He's in second place.
First place.
Number five.
Santander.
And that's a lot of money.
I got 22.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That would've been a close second.
Where'd you go, Number 4?
What?
Where?
He's really not here.
World Nagayama.
That's too bad.
First place.
Oh, no.
Where's World Nagayama?
He's gone?
He's gone.
This is it.
It's about seven pieces.
That's because it's not classy enough.
Well, I mean...
I mean, you've always been so good.
Not at all. So these popularity contests don't count for much, huh?
Well, yeah, well, well, sometimes I hit it.
Oh, really?
Can I have my 20,000 yen back?
Can I have it or can I have it back?
Yes, 80,000 more yen
But I forgot to ask for so much.
That's right.
I just had it.
I'll do it.
Do it! Do it!
Next.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Not like this.
It's gonna take too long.
Okay, two races.
Next five.
Subscribe to the Ana Channel.